Guide to the Consumer Reports. Audiovisual materials, 1940-2011 and undated RL.11802
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library
- Iron Mountain Indexed Materials, 1959-2005; undated; 4
  - XXAR_0053_TV_INT_Shapiro2--Esther K. Shapiro video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-215)
  - XXAR_0053_TV_INT_Shapiro2--Esther K. Shapiro video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0284)
  - XXAR_0054_TV_INT_Rice1--Florence Rice video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-210)
  - XXAR_0054_TV_INT_Rice1--Florence Rice video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0283)
  - XXAR_0055_TV_INT_Rice2--Florence Rice video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-209)
  - XXAR_0055_TV_INT_Rice2--Florence Rice video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0300)
  - XXAR_0056_TV_INT_Pittle1--David Pittle video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-208)
  - XXAR_0056_TV_INT_Pittle1--David Pittle video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0280)
  - XXAR_0057_TV_INT_Pittle2--David Pittle video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-214)
  - XXAR_0057_TV_INT_Pittle2--David Pittle video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0295)
  - XXAR_0058_TV_INT_Peterson1--Esther Peterson video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-207)
  - XXAR_0058_TV_INT_Peterson1--Esther Peterson video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0231)
  - XXAR_0059_TV_INT_Peterson2--Esther Peterson video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-206)
  - XXAR_0059_TV_INT_Peterson2--Esther Peterson video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0298)
  - XXAR_0060_TV_INT_Peterson--Esther Peterson, 1985 Dec. 13 (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0269)
  - XXAR_0060_TV_INT_Peterson--Esther Peterson, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-213)
  - XXAR_0061_TV_INT_Pertschuk1--Mike Pertschuk video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-205)
  - XXAR_0061_TV_INT_Pertschuk1--Mike Pertschuk video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0234)
  - XXAR_0061_TV_INT_Pertschuk2--Mike Pertschuk video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0246)
  - XXAR_0062_TV_INT_Pertschuk2--Mike Pertschuk video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-142)
  - XXAR_0063_TV_INT_Peabody1--Endicott Peabody video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-141)
  - XXAR_0063_TV_INT_Peabody1--Endicott Peabody video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0278)
  - XXAR_0064_TV_INT_Peabody2--Endicott Peabody video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-140)
  - XXAR_0064_TV_INT_Peabody2--Endicott Peabody video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0312)
  - XXAR_0065_TV_INT_OReilly1--Kathleen O'Reilly video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-139)
  - XXAR_0065_TV_INT_OReilly1--Kathleen O'Reilly video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0277)
  - XXAR_0066_TV_INT_OReilly2--Kathleen O'Reilly video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-138)
  - XXAR_0066_TV_INT_OReilly2--Kathleen O'Reilly video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0256)
  - XXAR_0067_TV_INT_Nishamura1--Glen Nishamura video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-137)
  - XXAR_0067_TV_INT_Nishamura1--Glen Nishamura video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0236)
  - XXAR_0068_TV_INT_Nishamura2--Glen Nishamura video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-136)
  - XXAR_0068_TV_INT_Nishamura2--Glen Nishamura video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0235)
  - XXAR_0069_TV_INT_Nelson1--Helen Nelson video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-135)
  - XXAR_0069_TV_INT_Nelson1--Helen Nelson video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0408)
  - XXAR_0070_TV_INT_Nelson2--Helen Nelson video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-134)
  - XXAR_0070_TV_INT_Nelson2--Helen Nelson video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0401)
  - XXAR_0071_TV_INT_Nader1--Ralph Nader video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-133)
  - XXAR_0071_TV_INT_Nader1--Ralph Nader video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0420)
  - XXAR_0072_TV_INT_Nader2--Ralph Nader video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-132)
  - XXAR_0072_TV_INT_Nader2--Ralph Nader video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0421)
  - XXAR_0073_TV_INT_Morse1--Richard L.D. Morse video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-131)
  - XXAR_0073_TV_INT_Morse1--Richard L.D. Morse video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0345)
  - XXAR_0074_TV_INT_Morse2--Richard L.D. Morse video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-130)
  - XXAR_0074_TV_INT_Morse2--Richard L.D. Morse video 2, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0352)
  - XXAR_0075_TV_INT_McEwen1--Robert J. McEwen S.J. video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-129)
  - XXAR_0075_TV_INT_McEwen1--Robert J. McEwen S.J. video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0331)
  - XXAR_0076_TV_INT_McEwen2--Robert J. McEwen S.J. video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-128)
  - XXAR_0076_TV_INT_McEwen2--Robert J. McEwen S.J. video 2, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0353)
  - XXAR_0077_TV_INT_McEldowney1--Ken McEldowney video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-127)
  - XXAR_0077_TV_INT_McEldowney1--Ken McEldowney video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0358)
  - XXAR_0078_TV_INT_McEldowney2--Ken McEldowney video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-126)
  - XXAR_0078_TV_INT_McEldowney2--Ken McEldowney video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0357)
  - XXAR_0079_TV_INT_Mathews1--Odonna Mathews video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-125)
  - XXAR_0079_TV_INT_Mathews1--Odonna Mathews video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0342)
  - XXAR_0080_TV_INT_Mathews2--Odonna Mathews video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-124)
  - XXAR_0080_TV_INT_Mathews2--Odonna Mathews video 2, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0351)
  - XXAR_0081_TV_INT_Layer1--Meredith M. Layer video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-123)
  - XXAR_0081_TV_INT_Layer1--Meredith M. Layer video 1, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0335)
  - XXAR_0082_TV_INT_Layer2--Meredith M. Layer video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-122)
  - XXAR_0082_TV_INT_Layer2--Meredith M. Layer video 2, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0344)
  - XXAR_0083_TV_INT_Knauer--Virginia Knauer video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-121)
  - XXAR_0083_TV_INT_Knauer--Virginia Knauer video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0433)
  - XXAR_0084_TV_INT_Karpatkin1--Rhoda Karpatkin video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-120)
  - XXAR_0084_TV_INT_Karpatkin1--Rhoda Karpatkin video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0415)
  - XXAR_0085_TV_INT_Karpatkin2--Rhoda Karpatkin video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-119)
  - XXAR_0085_TV_INT_Karpatkin2--Rhoda Karpatkin video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0431)
  - XXAR_0086_TV_INT_Jones1--Mary Gardiner Jones video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-118)
  - XXAR_0086_TV_INT_Jones1--Mary Gardiner Jones video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0413)
  - XXAR_0087_TV_INT_Jones2--Mary Gardiner Jones video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-117)
  - XXAR_0087_TV_INT_Jones2--Mary Gardiner Jones video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0410)
  - XXAR_0088_TV_INT_Jeffrey1--Mildred Jeffrey video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-116)
  - XXAR_0088_TV_INT_Jeffrey1--Mildred Jeffrey video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0407)
  - XXAR_0089_TV_INT_Jeffrey2--Mildred Jeffrey video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-115)
  - XXAR_0089_TV_INT_Jeffrey2--Mildred Jeffrey video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0414)
  - XXAR_0090_TV_INT_Herrera1--Pastor Herrera video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-114)
  - XXAR_0090_TV_INT_Herrera1--Pastor Herrera video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0429)
  - XXAR_0091_TV_INT_Herrera2--Pastor Herrera video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-113)
  - XXAR_0091_TV_INT_Herrera2--Pastor Herrera video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0402)
  - XXAR_0092_TV_INT_Hanggi1--Elena Hanggi video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-112)
  - XXAR_0092_TV_INT_Hanggi1--Elena Hanggi video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0435)
  - XXAR_0093_TV_INT_Hanggi2--Elena Hanggi video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-111)
  - XXAR_0093_TV_INT_Hanggi2--Elena Hanggi video 2, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0343)
  - XXAR_0094_TV_INT_Haas--Ellen Haas video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-110)
  - XXAR_0094_TV_INT_Haas--Ellen Haas video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0423)
  - XXAR_0095_TV_INT_Gregg1--Barbara Gregg video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-109)
  - XXAR_0095_TV_INT_Gregg1--Barbara Gregg video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0411)
  - XXAR_0096_TV_INT_Gregg2--Barbara Gregg video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-108)
  - XXAR_0096_TV_INT_Gregg2--Barbara Gregg video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0405)
  - XXAR_0097_TV_INT_Green1--Mark Green video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-107)
  - XXAR_0097_TV_INT_Green1--Mark Green video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0292)
  - XXAR_0098_TV_INT_Green2--Mark Green video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-106)
  - XXAR_0098_TV_INT_Green2--Mark Green video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0434)
  - XXAR_0099_TV_INT_Grant1--Susan Grant video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-105)
  - XXAR_0099_TV_INT_Grant1--Susan Grant video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0417)
  - XXAR_0100_TV_INT_Grant2--Susan Grant video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-104)
  - XXAR_0100_TV_INT_Grant2--Susan Grant video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0254)
  - XXAR_0101_TV_INT_Golodner1--Linda Golodner video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-101)
  - XXAR_0101_TV_INT_Golodner1--Linda Golodner video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0253)
  - XXAR_0102_TV_INT_Golodner2--Linda Golodner video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-103)
  - XXAR_0102_TV_INT_Golodner2--Linda Golodner video 2, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0252)
  - XXAR_0103_TV_INT_Fasse1--Bill Fasse video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-102)
  - XXAR_0103_TV_INT_Fasse1--Bill Fasse video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0247)
  - XXAR_0104_TV_INT_Fasse2--Bill Fasse video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-100)
  - XXAR_0104_TV_INT_Fasse2--Bill Fasse video 2, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0273)
  - XXAR_0105_TV_INT_Conran1--Jim Conran video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-099)
  - XXAR_0105_TV_INT_Conran1--Jim Conran video 1, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0242)
  - XXAR_0106_TV_INT_Conran2--Jim Conran video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-098)
  - XXAR_0106_TV_INT_Conran2--Jim Conran video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0416)
  - XXAR_0107_TV_INT_Claybrook1--Joan Claybrook video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-097)
  - XXAR_0107_TV_INT_Claybrook1--Joan Claybrook video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0409)
  - XXAR_0108_TV_INT_Claybrook2--Joan Claybrook video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-096)
  - XXAR_0108_TV_INT_Claybrook2--Joan Claybrook video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0406)
  - XXAR_0109_TV_INT_Brobeck1--Stephen Brobeck video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-095)
  - XXAR_0109_TV_INT_Brobeck1--Stephen Brobeck video 1, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0422)
  - XXAR_0110_TV_INT_Brobeck2--Stephen Brobeck video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-094)
  - XXAR_0110_TV_INT_Brobeck2--Stephen Brobeck video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0404)
  - XXAR_0111_TV_INT_Stark1--Tamra L. Stark video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-093)
  - XXAR_0111_TV_INT_Stark1--Tamra L. Stark video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0270)
  - XXAR_0112_TV_INT_Stark2--Tamra L. Stark video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-091)
  - XXAR_0112_TV_INT_Stark2--Tamra L. Stark video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0412)
  - XXAR_0112_TV_INT_Ulal3--Dom Ulal video 3, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-090)
  - XXAR_0112_TV_INT_Ulal3--Dom Ulal video 3, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0437)
  - XXAR_0113_TV_INT_Ulal4--Dom Ulal video 4, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-092)
  - XXAR_0113_TV_INT_Ulal4--Dom Ulal video 4, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0328)
  - XXAR_0114_TV_INT_Smith1--Ned Smith video 1, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-089)
  - XXAR_0114_TV_INT_Smith1--Ned Smith video 1, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0290)
  - XXAR_0115_TV_INT_Smith2--Ned Smith video 2, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-088)
  - XXAR_0115_TV_INT_Smith2--Ned Smith video 2, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0403)
  - XXAR_0139_TV_INT_Annual--Annual Meeting: 1) Report; 2) Tribute; 3) Parting Words; 4) Q&A; 5) Car/Auto; 6) Taste Test, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-087)
  - XXAR_0139_TV_INT_Annual--Annual Meeting: 1) Report; 2) Tribute; 3) Parting Words; 4) Q&A; 5) Car/Auto; 6) Taste Test, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0305)
  - XXAR_0173_TV_INT_Lab testing--Consumers Union lab testing, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-086)
  - XXAR_0173_TV_INT_Lab testing--Consumers Union lab testing, Undated (Box 97, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0289)
  - XXAR_0189_TV_INT_Knoll--Consumer Reports Auto Test Director Bob Knoll, Undated (Box 121, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-085)
  - XXAR_0189_TV_INT_Knoll--Consumer Reports Auto Test Director Bob Knoll, Undated (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-223)
  - XXAR_0192_TV_INT_Guest_ABC--Jim Guest interview, ABC News, WNN, Modern Marketing, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-323)
  - XXAR_0193_TV_PRO_Zillions_Toys--Zillions TV: A Kid's Guide to the Best Toys and Games, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-322)
  - XXAR_0195_TV_PRO_Zillions_Mall--Zillions Magazine mall rap commercial, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-321)
  - XXAR_0198_TV_PRO_Buy Me 3--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That 3! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-320)
  - XXAR_0199_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions and HBO: Kids and Cigarettes; Smoke Alarm: The Unfiltered Truth About Cigarettes, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-319)
  - XXAR_0201_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Teaching with Penny Power; Consumers Union Education Services master copy, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-318)
  - XXAR_0202_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Penny Power, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-317)
  - XXAR_0203_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Penny Power Fair, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-316)
  - XXAR_0204_TV_PRO_Dieting--HBO and Consumer Reports; Warning: Dieting May Be Hazardous to Your Health, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-315)
  - XXAR_0207_TV_PRO_Want to Know--Consumers Want to Know: Factual Description of Day-to-Day Work at Consumers Union, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-314)
  - XXAR_0210_TV_PRO_At a Glance--Consumers Union at a Glance, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-313)
  - XXAR_1192_TV_INT_Guest_ABC--Jim Guest interview, ABC News, WNN, Modern Marketing, 1993 Oct. 05 (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0329)
  - XXAR_1193_TV_PRO_Zillions_Toys--Zillions TV: A Kid's Guide to the Best Toys and Games, 1993 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0259)
  - XXAR_1193_TV_PRO_Zillions_Toys--Zillions TV: A Kid's Guide to the Best Toys and Games, 1993 Nov. 24 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0258)
  - XXAR_1193_TV_PRO_Zillions_Toys--Zillions TV: A Kid's Guide to the Best Toys and Games, 1993 Oct. 15 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0257)
  - XXAR_1195_TV_PRO_Zillions_Mall--Zillions Magazine mall rap commercial, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0442)
  - XXAR_1197_TV_PRO_Buy Me 2--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That Too! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1992 Feb. 14 (Box 93, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-227)
  - XXAR_1197_TV_PRO_Buy Me 2--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That Too! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, Undated (Box 89, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0268)
  - XXAR_1197_TV_PRO_Buy Me 2--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That Too! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, Undated (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0729)
  - XXAR_1198_TV_PRO_Buy Me 3--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That 3! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1992 Nov. 16 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-229)
  - XXAR_1198_TV_PRO_Buy Me 3--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That 3! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1993 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0264)
  - XXAR_1198_TV_PRO_Buy Me 3--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That 3! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, 1994 June 17 (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0244)
  - XXAR_1198_TV_PRO_Buy Me 3--Zillions and HBO: Buy Me That 3! A Kid's Survival Guide to TV Advertising, Undated (Box 91, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0260)
  - XXAR_1199_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions and HBO: Kids and Cigarettes; Smoke Alarm: The Unfiltered Truth About Cigarettes, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0400)
  - XXAR_1199_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions and HBO: Kids and Cigarettes; Smoke Alarm: The Unfiltered Truth About Cigarettes, Undated (Box 105, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0418)
  - XXAR_1199_TV_PRO_Zillions--Zillions and HBO: Kids and Cigarettes; Smoke Alarm: The Unfiltered Truth About Cigarettes, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0419)
  - XXAR_1201_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Teaching with Penny Power; Consumers Union Education Services, Undated (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-191)
  - XXAR_1201_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Teaching with Penny Power; Consumers Union Education Services, Undated (Box 83, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-192)
  - XXAR_1201_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Teaching with Penny Power; Consumers Union Education Services, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0339)
  - XXAR_1202_TV_PRO_ Penny Power--Penny Power, Undated (Box 95, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0438)
  - XXAR_1203_TV_PRO_Penny Power--Penny Power Fair, 1981 Nov. 19 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-238)
  - XXAR_1204_TV_PRO_Dieting--HBO and Consumer Reports; Warning: Dieting May Be Hazardous to Your Health, 1989 Aug. 08 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-239)
  - XXAR_1204_TV_PRO_Dieting--HBO and Consumer Reports; Warning: Dieting May Be Hazardous to Your Health, Undated (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0732)
  - XXAR_1207_TV_PRO_Want to Know--Consumers Want to Know: Factual Description of Day-to-Day Work at Consumers Union, 198 Nov. 22 (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-231)
  - XXAR_1207_TV_PRO_Want to Know--Consumers Want to Know: Factual Description of Day-to-Day Work at Consumers Union, Undated (Box 98, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-186)
  - XXAR_1210_TV_PRO_At a Glance--Consumers Union at a Glance, Undated (Box 122, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-312)
  - XXAR_1210_TV_PRO_At a Glance--Consumers Union at a Glance, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0322)
  - XXAR_1210_TV_PRO_At a Glance--Consumers Union at a Glance, Undated (Box 90, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0327)
- Product Testing and Reviews, 1941-2011; undated; 5
  - Automotive, 1967-2008; undated; 17
    - 1990 Recommended Cars, 1990 Mar. 20 (Box 45, Video-cassette RL11802-Umatic-099)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-235)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-225)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-226)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-227)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-228)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-229)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-230)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0648)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0649)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0650)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0996)
    - 2001 Mitsubishi Montero Limited, 2001 June 20 (Box 102, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0997)
    - 2006 B-Roll w/o Bug (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-267)
    - 6 Pickup Trucks Braking Turn One P.P.V. Avoidance Maneuver Trials, 1973 Sept. (Box 29, Film-reel RL11802-F8-013)
    - ABS Brakes Used Car Lemons, 1996 Feb. 05 (Box 66, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0145)
    - All Barrier Bumper Testing; Scenes from New Jersey, Undated (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F8-001)
    - Anti-Lock Brakes Smoke Detectors, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-192)
    - April Auto Issue B-Roll, 2008 (Box 1, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-011)
    - ATV Safety Institute, 2006 Mar. 20 (Box 101, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-275)
    - Australian Seat Belts but not version from which seat belts stock shots taken from, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-137)
    - Australian Seat Belts Where Have all the People Gone, Undated (Box 17, Film-reel RL11802-F16-079)
    - Australian Seat Belts Where Have all the People Gone, Undated (Box 34, Film-reel RL11802-F16-134)
    - Auto Child Restraints 3, Undated (Box 65, Film-reel RL11802-F16-189)
    - Auto Test, 2001 Mar. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-163)
    - Auto Test, 2001 Mar. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-171)
    - Auto Test, 2002 Feb. 21 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0747)
    - Auto Test 99, 1999 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-153)
    - Auto Test B-Roll, 1998 Mar. (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-194)
    - Auto Test Facility, 1999 June 03 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0643)
    - Auto Test Track Sample Clips, Undated (Box 99, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0919)
    - Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-151)
    - Auto Test Track Testing Demonstrations, 1999-2000 (Box 104, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-152)
    - Auto Test Tracks Testing Demonstration No Bug, 2005 (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-190)
    - Auto Testing, David Champion & Mike Quincy of Consume reports, 2003 Oct. 10 (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1195)
    - Auto Tires - Turtles, Undated (Box 18, Film-reel RL11802-F16-082)
    - Automobile Child Restraints, Undated (Box 14, Film-reel RL11802-F16-063)
    - Automotive B Roll, 2001 Apr. (Box 107, Video-cassette RL11802-Bcam-167)
    - Avalanche/SportTrac/Santa Fe and Partial Feb Details, Undated (Box 137, Optical-disc RL11802-OP-709)
    - Basher, Brakes, Turn 1, A.M., 1974 July (Box 29, Film-reel RL11802-F8-015)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, 2003 July (Box 103, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-1208)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0748)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0749)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0750)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0752)
    - Blind Spot Segments & Power-Window Segments, Undated (Box 100, Video-cassette RL11802-VHS-0770)